A Guide to the Papers of Norborne Berkeley 1918-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Business Papers 1916-1964
  - Subseries B: Oil and Gas Investments 1953-1964
    - Casey Law #1, Pottawatomie County, Oklahoma 1955-1957 (Box 104)
    - Drilling and Geological Reports on Troth #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 104)
    - Drilling and Geological Reports on Dillon #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1955 (Box 104)
    - Drilling and Geological Reports on Martin #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 104)
    - Drilling and Geological Reports on Reynolds #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 104)
    - Drilling Report, Mable Carr #1, Logan County, Oklahoma 1955 April 7 (Box 104)
    - West Big Hill Prospect, Jefferson County, Texas 1953-1964, 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Gas Contract of Texas Gas Pipe Line Corporation and Francis A. Calley et al. on the West Big Hill Area of Jefferson County, Texas 1954 May 4 (Box 105)
    - North Delhi Prospect, Harris County, Texas 1953-1962 (Box 105)
    - Diamond Island Prospect, Harris County, Texas 1953-1954 (Box 105)
    - West Columbia Prospect, Brazoria County, Texas 1954-1961 (Box 105)
    - Bay City Prospect, Matagorda County, Texas n.d. (Box 105)
      Map of Prospect
    - Bay City Prospect #1, Matagorda County, Texas 1954-1955 (Box 105)
    - Bay City Prospect #2, Matagorda County, Texas 1955 (Box 105)
    - The Regulation of Natural Gas by James W. McKie 1957 June (Box 105)
- Series IV: Financial Papers: Personal Accounts and Papers 1920-1963
  - Personal Accounts, Details of Expenses and Income 1936-1957, 5 folders (Box 106)
  - Personal Accounts, Details of Expenses and Income 1958-1959 (Box 107)
  - Personal Accounts 1960-1961 (Box 107)
  - Personal, Miscellaneous Investments and Securities Information 1939-1954 (Box 107)
  - Personal, Budgets 1938-1954 (Box 107)
  - Personal Business, Copy of Income Tax Returns 1920-1928, 9 folders (Box 107)
  - Personal Business, Copy of Income Tax Returns 1929-1943, 14 folders (Box 108)
  - Personal Business, Income Tax Returns for Employees of N.B. Household 1943-1945 (Box 108)
  - Personal Business, Copy of Income Tax Returns 1944-1949, 6 folders (Box 108)
  - Personal Business, Copy of Income Tax Returns 1950-1952, 3 folders (Box 109)
  - Personal Business, Copy of 1962 Income Tax Returns 1963 (Box 109)
  - Insurance Policies 1954-1955 (Box 109)
  - Checkbooks, Morgan, Guaranty and Trust of New York (Box 109)
  - Checkbooks, Morgan, Guaranty and Trust of New York (Box 110)
  - Checkbooks, First national Bank of Bethlehem, Pennsylvania (Box 111-113)
- Series V: Miscellaneous
  - Scrapbook Material (Box 114-116)
  - Photographs (Box Storage Box)